Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.17
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Ongoing Career, 1993; XVII.
  - Professional and Civic Work, 5.
    - Inter-American Development Bank
      - Meeting & notes: "CSIS Corruption Program in Latin America", December 3, 2007 (Box 1018, Folder 20)
      - Publications re: corruption and anticorruption efforts in Latin America, 2007 (Box 1018, Folder 21)
      - Organizational Functions document, December 12, 2007 (Box 1018, Folder 22)
      - Draft Outlines, December 9 - 13, 2007 (Box 1018, Folder 23)
      - Meeting at IADB with Jerry Butler (bio), Chair Audit Committee, December 12, 2007 (Box 1018, Folder 24)
      - New "Code of Ethics and Professional Conduct of IADB", December 13, 2007 (Box 1018, Folder 25)
      - Memos & Draft 6 "Report concerning Anti-Corruption Framework of IADB", January 2008 (Box 1018, Folder 26)
      - Paper May 8: "Fight Against Corruption: International Organizations at a Cross-roads", January 2008 (Box 1018, Folder 27)
      - Anti-corruption Newsletters, January - February 2008 (Box 1018, Folder 28)
      - Memos & correspondence re time required to complete external review of fraud & corruption. In bank-financed projects", January - February, 2008 (Box 1018, Folder 29)
      - Working draft: IDB report, January 22, 2008 (Box 1018, Folder 30)
      - Draft: Office of Institutional Integrity (OII) 2007 annual report, February 4, 2008 (Box 1018, Folder 31)
      - Draft IDB Report, February 27, 2008 (Box 1018, Folder 32)
      - Correspondence re: IDB contract, February - March 2008 (Box 1018, Folder 33)
      - Correspondence re: and copy of Revised Draft of IDB Report, February 20, 2008 (Box 1018, Folder 34)
      - March 7 draft report with correspondence & notes, February 7, 2008 (Box 1018, Folder 35)
      - Preliminary Report with memos and comments, March 14, 2008 (Box 1018, Folder 36)
      - Comments by Bank Units, May 16 - 25, 2008 (Box 1018, Folder 37)
      - March 14 Preliminary Report & comments & notes, May 27, 2008 (Box 1018, Folder 38)
      - Further notes and comments, June 3, 2008 (Box 1018, Folder 39)
      - Contract changes, May 30 - June 28, 2008 (Box 1018, Folder 40)
      - Preliminary report reflecting changes, June 3, 2008 (Box 1018, Folder 41)
      - Cumulative Blackline Report, June 22, 2008 (Box 1018, Folder 42)
      - July Preliminary Blackline Report with changes from March report, July 15, 2008 (Box 1018, Folder 43)
      - July Revised Report and related memos, July 2008 (Box 1018, Folder 44)
      - Misc. notes & communications, August 2008 (Box 1018, Folder 45)
      - Presentation to Audit Committee, October 28, 2008 (Box 1018, Folder 46)
      - (Final) Report concerning Anti-Corruption Framework of IADB, November 21, 2008 (Box 1018, Folder 47)
    - WorldCom Bankruptcy
      In August 2002, the U.S. Bankruptcy Court in the Southern District of New York appointed Thornburgh the examiner in the case filed by WorldCom, one of the world's largest telecommunications companies. This was a "sorry tale of corporate wrongdoing" (Evidence, p. 362). Thornburgh put together a team, with whom to undertake what he described a "massive task." "My job was to carry out an independent investigation into what happened in the WorldCom matter and to assure Bankruptcy Judge Arthur Gonzales that procedures and persons involved in any past wrongdoing were not carried forward into any reorganized entity… and finally to make recommendations to aid in avoiding repetition elsewhere of the acts that caused the downfall of WorldCom" (Evidence, p. 363). The three committee reports over several years place major responsibility for WorldCom's collapse on the members of the board of directors, especially those who served on its audit and compensation committees. Major officials involved in the fraud were convicted in federal court.
      - First Interim Report of Thornburgh, Bankruptcy Court Examiner, November 4, 2002 (Box 1019, Folder 1)
      - First Interim Report of Thornburgh, Bankruptcy Court Examiner (Thornburgh annotations), November 4, 2002 (Box 1019, Folder 2)
      - Memoranda and notes, February-April 2003 (Box 1019, Folder 3)
      - Emails regarding WorldCom, November 2003 (Box 1019, Folder 4)
      - Second Interim Report, June 9, 2003 (Box 1019, Folder 5)
      - Second Interim Report (Thornburgh annotations), June 9, 2003 (Box 1019, Folder 6)
      - "302 Interviews", ca. April 2003 (Box 1019, Folder 7)
      - "Restoring Trust" by Breeden, Corporate Monitor (re MCI), August 2003 (Box 1019, Folder 8)
      - "Claims by Dissenting Bondholders & Creditors", September 10, 2003 (Box 1019, Folder 9)
      - Third and FINAL Report, January 26, 2004 (Box 1019, Folder 10)
      - Executive Summaries of Reports of Dick Thornburgh, Bankruptcy Court Examiner, 2002-2004 (Box 1019, Folder 11)
      - Senate Judiciary Committee re WorldCom, Thornburgh Witness, July 22, 2003 (Box 1019, Folder 12)
      - Thornburgh Senate Testimony "as delivered", July 22, 2003 (Box 1019, Folder 13)
    - Ethics
      WorldCom and other corporate debacles and wrongdoing that were subsequently uncovered produced many legislative and regulatory responses. These included the Sarbanes-Oxley Act of 2002 and other regulations to avoid similar instances of corporate corruption. This section relates to relationships between corporations and their lawyers, and responsibilities, compensation, and liabilities of boards of directors. Thornburgh ultimately concluded that ethical conduct of corporate affairs would make more difference than all the laws and regulations and spoke often and wrote articles to this effect. The files date between 2003 and 2006.
      - Articles: Corporate Investigations, etc., 1999-2000 (Box 1020, Folder 1)
      - Breeden Report: "Corporate Governance for the Future of MCI", August 2003 (Box 1020, Folder 2)
      - Event: "Chief Legal Executive":General Counsel's Advisory Group, September 18, 2003 (Box 1020, Folder 3)
      - Event: ICI Independent Directors' Conference, October 16, 2003 (Box 1020, Folder 4)
      - World Com Lessons Learned: Thornburgh notes, October 29, 2003 (Box 1020, Folder 5)
      - ABA Meeting: Business Law Section, December 5, 2003 (Box 1020, Folder 6)
      - Business Week Interview re WorldCom & Ebbers Indictment, March 4, 2004 (Box 1020, Folder 7)
      - Ebbers Indictment Court Report, March 4, 2004 (Box 1020, Folder 8)
      - Articles: Ebbers, Ethics, Lessons for Lawyers, etc, March 12-18, 2004 (Box 1020, Folder 9)
      - Pittsburgh Athletic Assn event: Corporate Governance & Codes of Conduct, March 25, 2004 (Box 1020, Folder 10)
      - Duquesne Event: Thornburgh speech, "A Crisis in Corporate Governance - The WorldCom Experience", March 25, 2004 (Box 1020, Folder 11)
      - Articles re: Ethics, April 2004 (Box 1020, Folder 12)
      - CSIS Hills Program: Governance, Thornburgh Keynote Speaker, April 21, 2004 (Box 1020, Folder 13)
      - Corporate Counsel Forum "Crisis in Corporate America? Some Lessons from WorldCom", May 13, 2004 (Box 1020, Folder 14)
      - Woodstock Theological Center & Georgetown Law: "Crisis in Corporate Governance, October 12, 2004 (Box 1020, Folder 15)
      - Examiner Roundtable: "Role of Examiners and Lessons Learned", October 18, 2004 (Box 1020, Folder 16)
      - "Role of Government in Corporate Governance", November 2004 (Box 1020, Folder 17)
      - News articles, January-February 2005 (Box 1020, Folder 18)
      - Glasser Legal Works, Florida Business Law Section, Federal Securities Institute, Thornburgh remarks, February 16-18, 2005 (Box 1020, Folder 19)
      - CNBC: Thornburgh re: Ebbers Trial, March 4, 2005 (Box 1020, Folder 20)
      - CNBC: Ebbers Trial, March 8, 2005 (Box 1020, Folder 21)
      - CNBC: Ebbers Trial, March 15, 2005 (Box 1020, Folder 22)
      - PBS Nightly News: Ebbers Trial, March 15, 2005 (Box 1020, Folder 23)
      - CNBC: Ebbers Trial, March 18, 2005 (Box 1020, Folder 24)
      - Bankruptcy Bar Association of Southern District of Florida: Thornburgh speech "Crisis in Corporate America?", March 24, 2005 (Box 1020, Folder 25)
      - Articles, March 2005 (Box 1020, Folder 26)
      - Taping: Manulife/John Hancock re Internal Controls and Regulatory Compliance Enforcement, June 3, 2005 (Box 1020, Folder 27)
      - Articles, April -June 2005 (Box 1020, Folder 28)
      - Articles, July-September 2005 (Box 1020, Folder 29)
      - "Briefly": Sarbanes Oxley; Public Company Confidences, 2003-2005 (Box 1021, Folder 1)
      - Dover Management Radio Broadcase: Corporate Governance, August 18, 2005 (Box 1021, Folder 2)
      - Conference call: Senior Attorneys re. Evolving Government & Judicial Standards (Transcript included), September 8, 2005 (Box 1021, Folder 3)
      - Federation of Defense & Corporate Counsel, remarks, September 29, 2005 (Box 1021, Folder 4)
      - "Woodstock Evening of Conversation: Lawyers' Role in Preventing Corporate Fraud" (transcript), October 12, 2005 (Box 1021, Folder 5)
      - K&L Seminar: "Government & Internal Corporate Investigations", October 20, 2005 (Box 1021, Folder 6)
      - K&L Program San Francisco: "Ethics & Corporate Governance", November 9-10, 2005 (Box 1021, Folder 7)
      - Media Inquiry: "Corporate Governance: Enron, WorldCom, etc", November 29, 2005 (Box 1021, Folder 8)
      - 18th Annual Bankruptcy Symposium: Thornburgh speech, December 2, 2005 (Box 1021, Folder 9)
      - Article: UN Convention Against Corruption, December 5, 2005 (Box 1021, Folder 10)
      - Articles: Government and Ethics, 2006 (Box 1021, Folder 11)
      - Thornburgh notes re: CBS/Rather topic at event, April 4, 2006 (Box 1021, Folder 12)
      - Thornburgh article: "Organizing a Successful Corporate Internal Investigation", April 21, 2006 (Box 1021, Folder 13)
      - K&L Symposium: Government & Internal Corporate Investigations" (event data), May 4, 2006 (Box 1021, Folder 14)
      - K&L Symposium (continued): Thornburgh notes, May 4, 2006 (Box 1021, Folder 15)
      - K&L Sumposium (continued): memos and drafts, May 4, 2006 (Box 1021, Folder 16)
      - LRN-RAND Center on Corporate Ethics, May 11, 2006 (Box 1021, Folder 17)
      - Federalist Society & Shakespeare, May 31, 2006 (Box 1021, Folder 18)
      - K&L Associates re: "Handling High Profile Internal Investigations: From 60 Minutes to Athens Olympics", July 12, 2006 (Box 1021, Folder 19)
      - ACC Financial Services Committee Webcast: Key Issues in Internal Investigations, July 26, 2006 (Box 1021, Folder 20)
      - Articles: Corporate matters, August 2006 (Box 1021, Folder 21)
      - Metropolitan Corporate Counsel Article: "Compliance Readiness - General Counsel's Expanded Role", September 2006 (Box 1021, Folder 22)
      - Attorneys General Gonzales letter re "Thompson Memorandum" (Wall Street Journal?), September 9, 2006 (Box 1021, Folder 23)
      - K&L Program Dallas: Government & Internal Corporate Investigations", September 13, 2006 (Box 1021, Folder 24)
      - K&L Program Harrisburg: Internal Investigations, October 5, 2006 (Box 1021, Folder 25)
      - K&L Program San Francisco: Civil Privacy Issues, October 18, 2006 (Box 1021, Folder 26)
      - ACC-Corporate Counsel meeting, Philadelphia, November 13, 2006 (Box 1021, Folder 27)
      - Articles: Corporate governance, 2007 (Box 1021, Folder 28)
      - Articles: Securities Regulations, 2008 (Box 1021, Folder 29)
    - Dan Rather "60 Minutes Wednesday"
      Not long after the WorldCom matter was completed, Thornburgh was called by CBS News President Andrew Heyward, on September 21, 2004. He asked if Thornburgh would undertake an independent investigation with Associated Press CEO Lou Boccardi into preparation of the September 8 broadcast relating to the Texas Air National Guard Service of President George W. Bush, and public statements by CBS News following and defending the segment. This was extremely sensitive due to the proximity of the 2004 presidential election so work began immediately. The investigation revealed serious shortcomings. Ultimately Dan Rather relinquished his anchor position on the CBS Evening News and Mary Mapes and other senior individuals were terminated and/or resigned. Ultimately CBS News adopted all the recommendations in the final report which had received much public and news attention.
      - Report of Independent Review Panel, January 5, 2005 (Box 1021, Folder 30)
      - Speech and articles, 2004-2005 (Box 1021, Folder 31)
      - Related articles, 2007-2008 (Box 1021, Folder 32)
      - Related articles, 2012 (Box 1021, Folder 33)
    - Board of Science Applications Investigation of Greek Contract Issues
      - Independent Report re: Performance of contract between SAIC and Greek government, April 28, 2006 (Box 1021, Folder 34)
    - Russian Federation vs. Bank of New York
      A bizarre case involving U.S. Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations (RICO) statute took Thornburgh to the legal scene in the Russian Federation in 2008. In May 2007 a civil case was initiated in Moscow against Bank of New York Mellon. The complaint sought damages of $22.5 billion from the bank under the U.S. RICO statue. The bank's defense counsel engaged a number of experts in U.S. law to testify on its behalf, including Thornburgh, who went to Moscow and did testify, a copy of which is included here.
      - Expert witness statement of Thornburgh in Moscow Arbitrazh Court of Moscow, May 17, 2007 (Box 1021, Folder 35)
    - Freeh Report, re: Paterno
      Thornburgh was asked by the Paterno family to perform an independent and objective review of the "Freeh Report" regarding the University's response to child abuse charges and its references to Paterno. The ensuing report entitled "Review of the Freeh Report Concerning Joseph Paterno" is dated February 6, 2013 and describes the Freeh Report as seriously flawed.
      - Review of Freeh Report regarding Paterno, February 6, 2013 (Box 1021, Folder 36)
    - FBI Transformation Panel
      One of the constructive by-products of the dreadful 9/11 attacks was a top-to-bottom review of law enforcement and intelligence agencies, which included the Federal Bureau of Investigation. Thornburgh chaired this major review at the request of the National Academy of Public Administration (NAPA) of FBI's Director Bob Mueller's plans to make necessary improvements in the Bureau's processes and practices. This was an active and detailed process that extended from 2006-2010. There were several reports and multiple testimonies involved and are included here.
      - Binder: FBI Reorganization Panel: with early memo 6/21/01, re: K&L Electronic Document Management, June 5, 2002 (Box 1022, Folder 1)
      - Binder: 1st Panel Meeting. Assessment of FBI Reorganization Plan, June 17, 2002 (Box 1022, Folder 2)
      - Electronic Documents Management: memos, reports, June-August 2002 (Box 1022, Folder 3)
      - US House Appropriations Committee Hearing: reports, statements Thornburgh, Mueller etc. re: FBI reorganization, June 21, 2002 (Box 1022, Folder 4)
      - Meeting: Jeff Ritter re: Electronic Document Management, July 23, 2002 (Box 1022, Folder 5)
      - Meeting: Wilson Lowery re: FBI Cyber Update, July 23, 2002 (Box 1022, Folder 6)
      - Binder: 1st Panel Meeting. FBI Reorganization Plan, November 18, 2002 (Box 1022, Folder 7)
      - Binder: 2nd Panel Meeting. FBI Reorganization Plan, February 13, 2003 (Box 1022, Folder 8)
      - Presentation to National Academy for Public Administration (NAPA), February 13, 2003 (Box 1022, Folder 9)
      - Presentation to NAPA: background reports, February 13, 2003 (Box 1022, Folder 10)
      - Binder: 3rd Panel Meeting. FBI Reorganization Plan, May 12, 2003 (Box 1022, Folder 11)
      - Binder: 4th Panel Meeting. FBI Reorganization Plan, June 4, 2003 (Box 1022, Folder 12)
      - FBI Reorganization Plan Hearing. DT Testimony. House Committee on Appropriations, June 18, 2003 (Box 1022, Folder 13)
      - House Committee on Appropriations: Thornburgh testimony transcript, June 18, 2003 (Box 1022, Folder 14)
      - Testimony: summary statement…and previous testimony with annotations (June 21, 2002), June 18, 2003 (Box 1022, Folder 15)
      - Post 6/18/03 meeting memos, July 2003 (Box 1022, Folder 16)
      - Memo: Rick Schmitt, September 4, 2003 (Box 1022, Folder 17)
      - Panel Meeting at NAPA. Memoranda and notes, October 7, 2003 (Box 1022, Folder 18)
      - NAPA Fall Meeting and Presentation re: FBI Study, November 21, 2003 (Box 1022, Folder 19)
      - Memo & Article re: FBI Virtual Case File delay, December 2003 (Box 1022, Folder 20)
      - Intelligence Reform Programs at FBI, February 25, 2004 (Box 1022, Folder 21)
      - Memoranda & articles re: scope of NAPA FBI Study, March-May 2004 (Box 1022, Folder 22)
      - Binder: 1st Panel Meeting. FBI Transformation Study, March 24, 2004 (Box 1022, Folder 23)
      - Report: FBI Counter Terrorism Program since September 2001, April 14, 2004 (Box 1022, Folder 24)
      - Binder: 2nd Panel Meeting. FBI Transformation Study, May 3, 2004 (Box 1022, Folder 25)
      - NAPA Proposals re: budget structure, pay, personnel and Kinghorne testimony, May-June 2004 (Box 1022, Folder 26)
      - Binder: 3rd Panel Meeting. FBI Transformation Study, July 8, 2004 (Box 1022, Folder 27)
      - Binder: 4th Panel Meeting. FBI Transformation Study, September 8, 2004 (Box 1023, Folder 1)
      - NAPA/FBI Meeting: reports re: areas to be covered F/Y 2005, October 25, 2004 (Box 1023, Folder 2)
      - "Transforming the FBI: Progress & Challenges". Final Panel review draft, November 2004 (Box 1023, Folder 3)
      - December Progress Report memo, January 21, 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 4)
      - Report: Tranformation Study: Progress and Challenges, January-February 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 5)
      - Updates and articles re: "FBI Project", February 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 6)
      - Monthly reports re: FBI Study, February-April, 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 7)
      - Binder: lst Panel Meeting. FBI Transformation Study 2005, April 27, 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 8)
      - Mueller Testimony: Senate Appropriations Committee, Commerce, Justice, Science Subcommittee, June 5, 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 9)
      - Pre June 6 meeting information, April-June 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 10)
      - Public Disclosure Project/ Panel Discussions re: CIA/FBI Reform, June 6, 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 11)
      - Drafts & Transcript, re: Thornburgh remarks and correspondence, re: meeting, June 6, 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 12)
      - Post June 6 meeting articles and press clips, June 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 13)
      - WRNN-TV interview request re: CIA & FBI Reform, June 13, 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 14)
      - Thornburgh notes: Federal Times, Steve Losey interview, June 14, 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 15)
      - Meeting with Congressman Wolf re: state of FBI, June 16, 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 16)
      - Meeting Congressman Wolf & Lee Hamilton re: CIA & FBI Reform, June 20, 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 17)
      - FBI Human Capital Draft Report, June 22, 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 18)
      - FBI Human Capital Draft Report, July 11, 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 19)
      - Luncheon with Mueller, June 30, 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 20)
      - Binder: 2nd Panel Meeting. Transformation Study 2005, July 27, 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 21)
      - FBI Transformation Project, Progress Report, July 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 22)
      - Pre September 14 meeting: notes and articles, August-September 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 23)
      - GAO Study of FBI Enterprise Architecture, pre September meeting, September 9, 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 24)
      - Thornburgh statement draft for September 14 hearing, September 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 25)
      - Thornburgh Testimony, House Committee on Appropriations, September 14, 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 26)
      - Transcript: Mueller statements re: FBI fiscal year 2005 budget request, September 15, 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 27)
      - Binder: 3rd Panel Meeting. FBI Transformation Study, October 11, 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 28)
      - Articles and reports re: FBI, October-November 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 29)
      - Briefing with NAPA persons re: meeting with Director Mueller on November 30, November 28, 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 30)
      - Meeting with FBI Director Mueller re: field structure issues, November 30, 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 31)
      - Binder: 4th Panel Meeting. FBI Transformation Study 2005, December 16, 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 32)
      - Meeting with Mueller, December 19, 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 33)
      - FBI Transformation Project, Progress Report, December 28, 2005 (Box 1023, Folder 34)
      - NAPA/FBI Structure Subpanel Committee Meeting, February 10, 2006 (Box 1024, Folder 1)
      - Binder: Panel Meeting. FBI Transformation Study, March 9, 2006 (Box 1024, Folder 2)
      - Preliminary options for FBI structure, problem statements and notes, March 14, 2006 (Box 1024, Folder 3)
      - Meeting with Director Mueller, March 15, 2006 (Box 1024, Folder 4)
      - Meeting notes and reports re: FBI Transformation, April 18, 2006 (Box 1024, Folder 5)
      - Binder: Panel Meeting. FBI Transformation Study, June 21, 2006 (Box 1024, Folder 6)
      - Meeting drafts and notes; Interview with Jeff Brazil of Fast Company Magazine, June 27, 2006 (Box 1024, Folder 7)
      - Meeting notes and correspondence, June 29, 2006 (Box 1024, Folder 8)
      - Meeting with Mueller and Deputy Director, July 6, 2006 (Box 1024, Folder 9)
      - House Committee, Appropriations sub-committee. Testimony and drafts, September 14, 2006 (Box 1024, Folder 10)
      - Q&As for House Committee, Appropriations sub-committee, September 14, 2006 (Box 1024, Folder 11)
      - Corrected testimony, Q&As and paper submitted, September 14, 2006 (Box 1024, Folder 12)
      - Articles re: sub-committee meeting, September 14, 2006 (Box 1024, Folder 13)
      - "Transforming the FBI: Integrating Management Functions under Chief Management Officer", September 2006 (Box 1024, Folder 14)
      - Budget Formulation paper for Review, October 2006 (Box 1024, Folder 15)
      - FBI Transformation Papers, November 2006 (Box 1024, Folder 16)
      - Binder: Full Panel Meeting. FBI Transformation Study 2006, November 8, 2006 (Box 1024, Folder 17)
      - Two budget-related internal draft papers, November 17-20, 2006 (Box 1024, Folder 18)
      - Senate Judiciary Committee: FBI Oversight Hearing Summary, December 6, 2006 (Box 1024, Folder 19)
      - Final papers re: budget planning; Financial Management, December 11, 2006 (Box 1024, Folder 20)
      - NAPA Brochure: "Leaders", undated (Box 1024, Folder 21)
      - DOJ Audit Report: Internal Controls over Terrorism Reporting, February 2007 (Box 1024, Folder 22)
      - News articles re: FBI, March-April 2007 (Box 1024, Folder 23)
      - "Intelligence Products Paper", April 2007 (Box 1024, Folder 24)
      - DOJ follow-up Audit of FBI re Intelligence Analysts, April 2007 (Box 1025, Folder 1)
      - Memos & draft copy of IT Budget Process Integration Paper, April-May 2007 (Box 1025, Folder 2)
      - Final version: FBI Transformation Papers - Aligning IT Investment with Budget Formulation, May 2007 (Box 1025, Folder 3)
      - Binder: FBI Transformation Panel Meeting, June 13, 2007 (Box 1025, Folder 4)
      - FBI Report to DOJ: "…Critical End-State Capabilities FY 2009-2013. " Overview June 4, 2007, June 2007 (Box 1025, Folder 5)
      - Working draft: FBI Transformation Records Matrix, 2002-2007, June 1, 2007 (Box 1025, Folder 6)
      - Memo: Budget Process Review. Ongoing tasks FY 2008, January 13, 2008 (Box 1025, Folder 7)
      - NAPA / FBI Panel Meeting, April 8, 2008 (Box 1025, Folder 8)
      - FBI Transformation Study: Budget Process Review Sub-Panel Meeting, April 8, 2008 (Box 1025, Folder 9)
      - Memos, articles and reports: FBI Panel Meeting and earlier reports and comments, April 2008 (Box 1025, Folder 10)